Guide to the Stanley Milgram Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General Files, 1954-1985; Series I
  - Alphabetical
    - Moscovici, Serge, 1963-1982 (Box 18, Folder 266)
    - New Ideas in Psychology, Undated (Box 18, Folder 267)
    - Photographs of Milgram, 1960-1978, undated (Box 18, Folder 268)
      See also: Oversize
    - Photographs of students and staff at CUNY, Circa 1970s (Box 18, Folder 269)
    - Photographs, unidentified, 1965-1982, undated (Box 18, Folder 270)
    - Photographs, unidentified, Undated (Box 18, Folder 271)
    - Photographs, unidentified, Undated (Box 18, Folder 272)
    - Poems, Undated (Box 18, Folder 273)
    - Recommendations, Circa 1964-1984 (Box 19, Folder 274-296)
      Conditions Governing Access
      These records are restricted until 2060.
    - Recommendations, Circa 1964-1984 (Box 20, Folder 297-325)
    - Sherif, Muzafer, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 326)
    - Silver, Maury, 1971-1984, undated (Box 21, Folder 327)
      - Interview with Stanley Milgram, Undated; 1 (Box 21a)
        Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
        - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 21aD)
    - Subject recruitment techniques, 1968-1970, undated (Box 21, Folder 328)
    - Teitlebaum: Harvard course in physiological psychology, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 328a)
    - Twentieth Century Fund. Project on News Agencies (Edward J. Epstein), 1976-1980 (Box 21, Folder 329)
    - Urban dogs, 1973-1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 330)
    - University of Pennsylvania: review committee for the Department of Psychology, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 331)
    - Video tape, unidentified
      See: Unidentified video tapes
    - Visual-Verbal Workshop, 1967, undated (Box 21, Folder 332)
    - Visual-Verbal Workshop, 1967, undated (Box 21, Folder 333)
    - Vita, 1955-1979, undated (Box 21, Folder 334)
    - Writings on Milgram or his work
      - 1962-1964 (Box 21, Folder 335)
      - 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 336)
      - 1967 (Box 21, Folder 337)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 338)
      - 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 339)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 340)
      - 1975 (Box 22, Folder 341)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 342)
      - 1978 (Box 22, Folder 343)
      - 1979 (Box 22, Folder 344)
      - 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 345)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 346)
      - No date (Box 22, Folder 347)
      - "Mind's Eye of New York": correspondence, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 348)
      - Psychology Today interview: correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 349)
      - Psychology Today interview: manuscript drafts, Undated (Box 22, Folder 350)
      - Psychology Today interview: printed copies, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 351)
      - BBC - Horizon, Christopher La Fontaine, 1972-1974, undated (Box 22, Folder 352)
      - BBC - Horizon, Milgram's notes, 1974, undated (Box 22, Folder 353)
      - BBC - Horizon, script, 1974, undated (Box 22, Folder 354)
      - "Experimenting with Man" in Yale Scientific, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 355)
      - "A Psychologist Looks at Photography" in The New Art Examiner: printed copy, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 356)
      - "A Psychologist Observes Photography" in Camera: correspondence, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 357)
      - "A Psychologist Observes Photography" in Camera: manuscript draft, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 358)
      - " A Psychologist Observes Photography" in Camera: printed copies, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 359)
      - Mental Maps of New York: correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 360)
      - Mental Maps of New York: illustrations, Undated (Box 22, Folder 361)
      - Mental Maps of New York: illustrations layout, Undated (Box 22, Folder 362)
      - Mental Maps of New York: manuscript drafts, Undated (Box 23, Folder 363)
      - Mental Maps of New York: manuscript drafts, 1977, undated (Box 23, Folder 364)
      - Mental Maps of New York: printed copies, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 365)
      - Current Biography: printed copy, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 366)
      - "The High Priest of Guerrilla Psych" in OMNI: correspondence, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 367)
      - "The High Priest of Guerrilla Psych" in OMNI: manuscript draft, 1979, undated (Box 23, Folder 368)
      - "The High Priest of Guerrilla Psych" in OMNI: printed copies, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 369)
      - "Talk of the Town" in The Sciences: printed copy, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 370)
      - Contemporary Authors, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 371)
      - "Understanding Psychological Man" in Psychology Today; correspondence, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 372)
      - "Understanding Psychological Man" in Psychology Today: manuscript drafts, Undated (Box 23, Folder 373)
      - "Understanding Psychological Man" in Psychology Today: printed copies, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 374)
      - Scott, Foresman and Company, interview: correspondence, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 375)
      - Scott, Foresman and Company, interview; manuscript draft, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 376)
      - Stockholm, Modig interview, 1982, undated (Box 23, Folder 377)
      - NPR piece on Kitty Genovese: Milgram interview (brief statement as part of larger piece), Circa 1983 (Box 23, Folder 378)
        - Preservation master, 1
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 23.378U)
      - Who's Who in America, 1979-1983 (Box 23, Folder 379)
      - "Ruminations On Rudeness" in Bottom Line: manuscript draft, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 380)
      - "Ruminations On Rudeness" in Bottom Line: printed copies, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 381)
      - Unidentified interviews (fragments), 1977, undated (Box 23, Folder 382)
    - Unidentified, 1966-1984, undated (Box 23, Folder 383)
    - Unidentified video tapes, Undated (Box 23a)
- Studies, 1927-1984; Series II
  The material in this series is arranged by study title in alphabetical order. For each study, material is organized by document type and listed in alphabetical order.
  - Computerized Asch experiment, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Crowds
    - Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Data analysis, Circa 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
    - Films, Circa 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
    - Financial records, 1968-1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Notes, Circa 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, Circa 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 9-10)
  - Cyranic
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - CUNY. Committee on Protection of Human Subjects; Office of Sponsored Research, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - CUNY. Committee on Protection of Human Subjects; Office of Sponsored Research, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - National Science Foundation, 1979 February-August (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - National Science Foundation, 1979 October-1980 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Data
      See: Series V
    - Data analysis, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 16-17)
    - Data analysis: experiment 1, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Data analysis: condition 2, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Data analysis: cyranic attribution, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Equipment, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Forms, instructions, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Forms, instructions: cyranic attribution (experiment 1), 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Forms, instructions: young cyranoid (condition 2), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Grants: drafts of and notes for proposals, Circa 1977-1982 (Box 25, Folder 25-27)
    - Grants: PSC-CUNY Research Award proposal, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Grants: video tape for NSF review panel, "Cyranic Speech: Pilot Studies", 2 videotapes (Half-inch), Circa 1977 (Box 26.1–26.2)
      - Duplicating master, 2 (Box 26.1D–26.2D)
      - Use copy, 2 (Box 26.1U–26.2U)
    - Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Notes, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Notes: young cyranoid, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Subject recruitment, Circa 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Recordings
      - Cyranic discussions, 1981; 1 (Box 26.3)
        - Duplicating master, 8
        - Use copy, 8 (Box 26.3U)
      - Cyranic tapes I, 1981 Spring; 1 (Box 26.4)
      - Cyranic discussion, 1981 May 1; 1 (Box 26.5)
      - Cyranic discussions II, [1981] May 6; 1 (Box 26.6)
      - Subject recruitment, Jason, 1983 November; 1 (Box 26.7)
      - Cyranoid participants #2, 1983 November 8; 1 (Box 26.8)
      - [Participants?] 8-14, Jocelyn and William, 1983 November 29; 1 (Box 26.9)
      - Omnri Cyranoid, 1984 March 31; 1 (Box 26_10)
      - Cyranic I, 1981 April 27; 1 (Box 26.11)
      - Cyranic II, Circa 1981 April; 1 (Box 26.12)
      - Cyranic III, Circa 1981 April; 1 (Box 26.13)
      - Tapes, video: "The Cyranic Mode", Undated (Box 27, Folder 38-41)
      - Tapes, video: Young Cyranoid audition tapes, 1984 March 31; 5 (Box 28.1–28.5)
        - Duplicating master, 5 (Box 28.1D–28.5D)
        - Use copy, 5 (Box 28.1U–28.5U)
      - Tapes, video: unidentified, Undated (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Transcripts: young cyranoid, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Writings of others, 1955-1971, undated (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Group influence over time
    - Apparatus, Undated (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Data
    - Notes, Undated (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Group presssure, tone length, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Interocular time gap
    - Data analysis, Undated (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Equipment, 1966-1969 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Film, Undated (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Forms, instructions, Undated (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Grant proposal, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Notebook, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Notes, 1968-1969, undated (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - Subject recruitment, Undated (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Writings of others, 1964-1969 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Lost letter
    - General, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - German, Undated (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Integration, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Overseas Chinese
      - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 62)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 63)
      - Notes, Circa 1966 (Box 29, Folder 64)
      - Reports and results, 1963-1964, undated (Box 29, Folder 65)
      - Sample documents, 1964-1966, undated (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Writings of others, 1971-1982, undated (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - Mescaline
    - Correspondence and grant proposal, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 68)
    - Data
    - Notes, 1961, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - New York-Paris
    - New York City Image
      - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 70)
      - Data analysis
        - Coding, Undated (Box 29, Folder 71)
        - Computer printouts, Undated (Box 30)
        - Description of New York, Undated (Box 31, Folder 72)
        - Location identification, Undated (Box 31, Folder 73)
        - Pre-pilot, Undated (Box 31, Folder 74)
        - Pilot, Undated (Box 31, Folder 75)
        - Respondents, Undated (Box 31, Folder 76)
        - Set I, Undated (Box 31, Folder 77)
        - Set II, Undated (Box 31, Folder 78)
      - Locations, Undated (Box 31, Folder 79)
      - Notes, Undated (Box 31, Folder 80)
      - Photographs and maps, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 81)
        General note
        See also: box 145, folder 2
      - Questionnaire and script design, Undated (Box 31, Folder 82)
      - Questionnaire design: slides, Undated (Box 32)
      - Subject recruitment, 1970, undated (Box 33, Folder 83)
      - Writings of others, references, 1967-1970, undated (Box 33, Folder 84)
    - New York Mental Maps
      - Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 33, Folder 85)
      - Data analysis
        - General, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 86)
        - 1st questionnaire
          - Index cards, Undated (Box 34–36)
          - Notebooks, Undated (Box 37, Folder 87-88)
        - 2nd questionnaire
          - Index cards, Undated (Box 38–39)
          - Computer printout, 1976 March 3 (Box 40, Folder 89)
          - Computer printout, Alice Kornblith, 1975 February 27 (Box 40, Folder 90)
          - Notebooks, Undated (Box 40, Folder 91-92)
      - Grant: drafts, 1975, undated (Box 40, Folder 93)
      - Grant: monthly fiscal reports, 1975-1977, undated (Box 40, Folder 94)
      - Notes, Undated (Box 40, Folder 95)
      - Questionnaire design, Undated (Box 40, Folder 96)
      - Subject recruitment, Undated (Box 40, Folder 97)
      - Writings of others, references, 1972-1977, undated (Box 40, Folder 98)
    - Paris study
      - Correspondence, general, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 99)
      - Correspondence, general, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 100)
      - Correspondence, general, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 101)
      - Correspondence, general, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 102)
      - Data analysis
        - By quartier, 1976, undated (Box 41, Folder 103)
        - Coding manual, 1973, undated (Box 41, Folder 104)
        - Endroits privées, Undated (Box 41, Folder 105)
        - Etude sur L'Image de Paris, 1973 August 8
          See: box 145, folder 4
        - Etude sur L'Image de Paris: dépouillments complémentaires, volume 1, 1973 August 20
          See: box 145, folder 5
        - Frequency of elements, Undated (Box 41, Folder 106)
        - Links, Undated (Box 41, Folder 107-108)
        - Notebook, Undated (Box 41, Folder 109)
        - Photograph identification, Undated (Box 41, Folder 110)
        - Qualitative comments, Undated (Box 41, Folder 111-112)
        - Rides and walks, 1973, undated (Box 42, Folder 113)
          See also: box 145, folder 3
        - Spontaneous categories of Paris, Undated (Box 42, Folder 114)
        - Tracings of Seine, Undated (Box 42, Folder 115)
        - Cartes Mentales et Images Sociales de Paris, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 116)
      - Maps, 1957-1972, undated (Box 42, Folder 117)
      - Notes, Undated (Box 42, Folder 118)
      - Personnel, Undated (Box 42, Folder 119)
      - Questionnaire design, Undated (Box 42, Folder 120)
      - Questionnaire design: slides used for photographic identification, Undated (Box 42, Folder 121)
      - Subject recruitment, 1970, undated (Box 43, Folder 122)
      - Writings of others, references, 1951-1975, undated (Box 43, Folder 123)
  - Norwegian-French study
    - Data
    - Notes and data analysis, 1956-1959, undated (Box 43, Folder 124-125)
  - Obedience
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 126)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 127)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 128)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 43, Folder 129)
    - Data
    - Data analysis
      - Coded comments of subjects, Undated (Box 44)
      - Computer printouts
        See: box 145, folder 6-9
      - Condition 01, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 130)
      - Condition 02, voice feedback, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 131)
      - Condition 03, proximity, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 132)
      - Condition 04, touch proximity, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 133)
      - Condition 05, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 134)
      - Condition 06, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 135)
      - Condition 07, groups for obedience, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 136)
      - Condition 08, "I sign on condition you let me...", Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 137)
      - Condition 09, groups for obedience, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 138)
      - Condition 10, benign experimenter, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 139)
      - Condition 11, group choice, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 140)
      - Condition 12, authority as victim, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 141)
      - Condition 13, OB group, teach 1 "No Trigger for N. S.", Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 142)
      - Condition 14, carte blanche, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 143)
      - Condition 15, double authority, common man shocked, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 144)
      - Condition 16, double authority, experimenter shocked, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 145)
      - Condition 17, common man authority I, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 146)
      - Condition 18, experimenter departs, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 147)
      - Condition 19, no experimenter, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 148)
      - Condition 20, female, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 149)
      - Condition 21, prediction of behavior, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 150)
      - Condition 22, common man authority II, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 151)
      - Condition 23, Bridgeport, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 152)
      - Condition 24, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 153)
      - Duration, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 154)
      - Maximum shock, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 155)
      - Responsibility clock, Circa 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 156)
      - Statistical analysis, Circa 1962 (Box 45, Folder 157-158)
    - Forms, mailings, Undated (Box 45, Folder 159)
    - Grants, 1961-1967 (Box 45, Folder 160)
    - Instructions and procedures, Undated (Box 45, Folder 161)
    - Long interviews, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 162)
    - Notebook, 1961-1970 (Box 46, Folder 163)
    - Notes
      - General, 1961-1962 (Box 46, Folder 164-165)
      - Action conformity, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 166)
      - Antecedent conditions, 1961-1963 (Box 46, Folder 167)
      - Binding, 1961-1968 (Box 46, Folder 168)
      - Community impact, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 169)
      - Consequences, 1962-1963 (Box 46, Folder 170)
      - Breakoff types, Undated (Box 46, Folder 171)
      - Bridgeport experiments, Undated (Box 46, Folder 172)
      - Ethics, 1962-1966 (Box 46, Folder 173)
      - Method, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 174)
      - Proximity, 1955, 1964, undated (Box 46, Folder 175)
      - Resolving mechanisms, 1962-1968 (Box 46, Folder 176)
      - Role permutations, Undated (Box 46, Folder 177)
    - Photographic negatives and slides, Undated (Box 46, Folder 178)
    - Questionnaire analysis, Undated (Box 47, Folder 179)
    - Subject recruitment, 1960, undated (Box 47, Folder 180)
    - Writings of others
      - A-B, 1943-1979 (Box 47, Folder 181)
      - C-F, 1961-1983, undated (Box 47, Folder 182)
      - G-H, 1961-1979 (Box 47, Folder 183)
      - K-L, 1961-1976, undated (Box 47, Folder 184)
      - M, 1940-1976 (Box 47, Folder 185)
      - N-R, 1927-1982 (Box 47, Folder 186)
      - S-Z, 1970-1977, undated (Box 47, Folder 187)
      - Unidentified, Undated (Box 48, Folder 188)
      - Quotes and references, 1962-1963, undated (Box 48, Folder 189)
  - Promissory note, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 190)
  - Risk taking
    - Data
  - Small World
    - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 48, Folder 191)
    - Data
    - Forms, mailings, 1967, undated (Box 48, Folder 192)
    - Forms, mailings, 1965-1966, undated (Box 48, Folder 193)
    - Grants: Korte study, 1966-1967 (Box 48, Folder 194)
    - Data analysis: Los Angeles, 1967 October (Box 48, Folder 195)
    - Data analysis: Nebraska study, 1967 March 17
      See: Oversize
    - Notes, 1966, undated (Box 48, Folder 196)
    - Notes: Kansas study, 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 197)
    - Notes: Korte study, Undated (Box 48, Folder 198)
    - Notes: Nebraska study, Undated (Box 48, Folder 199)
    - Notes: Nebraska study, Undated (Box 48, Folder 200)
    - Subject recruitment, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 201)
    - Writings of others, 1961-1966, undated (Box 48, Folder 202)
    - Writings of others, 1967, undated (Box 48, Folder 203)
    - Writings of others, 1975-1981 (Box 49, Folder 204)
    - Writings of others, 1968, undated (Box 49, Folder 205)
  - TV Violence
    - Correspondence: general, 1969-1973 (Box 49, Folder 206)
    - Correspondence: CBS, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 207)
    - Correspondence: CBS, 1970-1971 (Box 49, Folder 208)
    - Correspondence: CBS, 1972-1974 (Box 49, Folder 209)
    - Correspondence: Project Hope, 1970-1971 (Box 49, Folder 210)
    - Correspondence: Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 211)
    - Correspondence: Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 212)
    - Correspondence: Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1971-1974 (Box 49, Folder 213)
    - Data analysis, Undated (Box 50, Folder 214)
    - Data analysis: composite response to stimulus programs, Undated (Box 50, Folder 215)
    - Design/procedures: donation boxes, 1970-1972 (Box 50, Folder 216)
    - Design/procedures: field lab and office design, Circa 1970 (Box 50, Folder 217)
    - Design/procedure: master of ceremonies message, Undated (Box 50, Folder 218)
    - Design/procedures: prizes, Circa 1970 (Box 50, Folder 219)
    - Design/procedures: taping systems, answering machines, Undated (Box 50, Folder 220)
    - Fiscal reports, monthly, 1969-1972 (Box 50, Folder 221)
    - Notebook, Circa 1970-1972 (Box 50, Folder 222)
    - Notebook, Circa 1970-1972 (Box 50, Folder 223)
    - Notebook, Circa 1971 (Box 50, Folder 224)
    - Notebook: drafts, Circa 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 225)
    - Notes, Circa 1969-1970 (Box 50, Folder 226)
    - Notes: California trip, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 227)
    - Personnel, 1969-1971 (Box 50, Folder 228)
    - Subject recruitment, Circa 1970 (Box 50, Folder 229)
    - Stimulus material: film, Undated (Box 51, Folder 230)
    - Stimulus program, 1969-1970 (Box 51, Folder 231)
    - Stimulus program: script, version 1, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 232)
    - Stimulus program: script, version 2, 1970 May 25 (Box 51, Folder 233)
    - Stimulus program: script, version 3, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 234)
    - Stimulus program: version 2, 1970 September 25 (Box 51.6–51.7)
      - Duplicating master, videotape (VHS) (Box 51.6D)
      - Use copy, videotape (VHS) (Box 51.6U)
    - Stimulus program: version 3, 1970 September 23 (Box 51.7)
      - Duplicating master, videotape (VHS) (Box 51.7D)
      - Use copy 1, videotape (VHS) (Box 51.7U1)
      - Use copy 2, videotape (VHS) (Box 51.7U2)
    - Study conditions
      - BRASS: notes, 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 237)
      - BRASS pilot: subject recruitment and design/procedures, Circa 1971 (Box 51, Folder 238)
      - BRASS, NY: subject recruitment; design/procedures, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 239)
      - BRASS, NY: data analysis, Circa 1971 (Box 51, Folder 240)
      - BRASS, St. Louis: subject recruitment; design/procedures, Circa 1971 (Box 51, Folder 241)
      - BRASS, St. Louis: data analysis, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 242)
      - CRASS I: subject recruitment, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 243)
      - CRASS I: design/procedures, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 244)
      - CRASS I: data analysis, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 245)
      - CRASS II: data analysis, Circa 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 246)
      - CLOD: subject recruitment, 1970 November 16 (Box 52, Folder 247)
      - CLOD: design/procedures, Undated (Box 52, Folder 248)
      - CLOD: data analysis, Undated (Box 52, Folder 249)
      - FRUS: design/procedures, Circa 1971 (Box 52, Folder 250)
      - FRUS: subject recruitment, Circa 1971 (Box 52, Folder 251)
      - FRUS: data analysis, Circa 1971 (Box 52, Folder 252)
      - Hotel study, Circa 1971 (Box 52, Folder 253)
      - Hotel study: data analysis, 1971 October 4-1971 October 8 (Box 52, Folder 254-256)
      - MOD, Circa 1971 (Box 52, Folder 257)
      - MOD: data analysis, Circa 1971 (Box 52, Folder 258)
      - Telephone study: correspondence, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 259)
      - Telephone study: data collection, Circa 1971 (Box 52, Folder 260)
      - Telephone study: notes, Circa 1971 (Box 53, Folder 261)
      - Telephone study: newspaper ad, Circa 1971 (Box 53, Folder 262)
      - Telephone study: TV spot, Circa 1971 (Box 53, Folder 263)
      - Telephone study: TV spot, film of previous Project Hope public services spots, Undated (Box 53, Folder 264)
      - Telephone study: TV spot, 16mm film, ca. 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 265)
      - Telephone study: TV spot, video master
        See: box 150
      - Telephone study: TV spot, video E.E. master
        See: box 151